-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
[screeches]
-[Kenji whimpering]
-It's okay. It's okay.
-We're all okay. [whimpers]
-[snarling]
Kenji, those bones--
check for a raptor skull.
What?
In the video game, I--
You wanna talk about video games now?
-[screeches]
-[yelps]
[grunts, pants]
[Kenji] No! Let me out! Let me out!
-[yelps]
-[screeches]
[both whimpering]
-[screeching]
-[whimpers]
[Roxie] Hey, come and get it!
-[screeching]
-[snarls]
-Get out of there!
-[screeches]
[both screaming]
[panting]
[tires screech]
-[man 1] Secure the paddock!
-[man 2] Move!
[man 3] This way!
-[man 2] Come on, move!
-Dave, that was...
Thank you so much.
Oh, that's standard procedure, Darius.
I do that kind of stuff all the time.
Give me a second. [vomits]
[retches]
That's better.
-[Dave grunts]
-[pants]
Are you hurt?
Is everyone all right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where do you think you're going?
-You and Darius are in big trouble.
-I--
-But he-- he was--
-Save it!
We'll decide what to do with you later.
If you even get to remain here
after a stunt like this.
[door alarm beeps]
[snarling]
[Kenji pops lips]
[popping continues]
How could you do something so stupid?
I do a lot of stupid things,
so you'll have to be
a little more specific than that.
Girls love a grand gesture, junior.
-You'll understand when you're older.
-[sighs]
Okay, maybe it wasn't my best idea.
Look, I don't wanna get kicked out either.
When my dad...
My whole life, I've been trying
to make him proud.
If he finds out
that I messed up again, he might...
finally give up on me for good.
[door opens]
We gave Brooklynn a warning
for sneaking out,
-but what you two chuckleheads did--
-Especially you, Kenji!
Your recklessness put yours, Darius,
and Dave's lives in danger!
-We should call your parents--
-It was my fault!
I jumped into the pit.
Kenji was...
trying to save me.
Yeah, that's it.
I... I was saving the poor,
confused little kid.
I'm sorry, so,
Darius the dino-genius was saved
by Kenji, the kid who thinks dinosaurs
went extinct because, and I quote,
"Their farts turned the air trashy"?
-Prove me wrong, yo.
-[sighs]
Yeah, it's just that Brooklynn's account
is quite different from yours.
Pfft! Brooklynn.
Look, it was dark, she was confused,
she needs glasses. [chuckles]
Vanity, am I right?
What's important is that I'll keep
looking out for the kid, here.
You're welcome.
[Roxie] Mm-hmm.
No harm, no foul. Let's chalk
the whole thing up to experience.
Lessons, friendships--
this is what camp's about!
-Who's with me?
-Fine.
But one more misstep...
-I... We won't let you down.
-[pops lips]
So, what are we doing tomorrow?
[flies buzzing]
[Roxie] Enjoy cleaning this up, boys.
[retches]
We're going to the genetics lab.
[camera shutter clicks]
Cologne. That'll help with the smell.
And the ladies. What-what?
But mostly the smell.
The stench of dinosaur poo
can really linger.
-What? But... [sighs]
-[engine starts]
Ugh! Gross.
Ugh. I'm still dropping followers?
"When are we gonna see cool stuff"?
Chill, dude. I just got here.
So, what's your next video?
Ooh, maybe there's baby dino eggs
in the lab.
Everyone loves a baby video.
-Whatever it is, it'll be cool.
-[Ben humming]
[humming stops]
Sanitizer.
Who knows what kind
of creepy dino goo is at that lab?
Gotta be ready for anything.
The world is a grab-bag of gross,
and we're all just along for the moist,
sticky roller coaster ride called life.
Mm. Hmm. Hmm.
[Brooklynn] What's good, Brooklanders?
Today, I'm coming to you
from one of Jurassic World's
coolest remote genetics labs!
-[equipment trilling]
-[Sammy gasps]
It's so shiny in here!
This is a rare window
into the park's inner workings.
Not just anyone can come here, you know.
Yep, this is where the magic happens.
Doc Wu-Wu!
Guess who's ready to have
a blastocyst from the pastocyst?
The mitosis with the mosisis!
We're ready for some chromosomes,
my bro-mosome.
Wu, there it is!
-I can do more.
-Please don't.
We're here for the tour, Dr. Wu.
Camp Cretaceous?
Ms. Dearing should have mentioned.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Masrani
has accelerated the timetable
for our newest exhibit yet again.
I simply don't have time to spend
the afternoon babysitting children.
-Young lady, no recording in the lab.
-Huh?
But that's kind of my whole deal.
You see, I have my own web channel--
And that's germane because...?
[sighs] I'm sorry, Doctor.
I just wanted my followers
to meet the genius
who brought dinosaurs back to life.
I mean, without you,
there is no Jurassic World.
But, hey, if you wanna toil in the shadows
while Masrani and John Hammond
get all the credit, I respect that.
It's about the work.
How many people watch
this web show of yours?
-[flies buzzing]
-[Darius grunts]
This bites!
Thanks to you, I'm shoveling poop
instead of watching a live dinosaur birth.
That's only been my dream
since, uh, I don't know... forever!
Dude, that's not a dream.
A dream is like when you save
mermaids from a shark.
Whatever!
Figures you wouldn't understand.
The scientists are heroes.
They recreated the T. rex!
A T. rex!
Do you know what it takes to do that?
It's cute you're this excited
about some dumb lab.
Noobs like you don't know
half of what's in this place.
-Like what?
-[snickers]
[scoffs] You're all talk.
I've been to this park,
like, 50 kajillion times.
I'm in the know, junior.
And since you helped me out earlier,
I might be willing to show you
the good stuff.
No. No way.
I cannot get into more trouble.
Eh. Hey, suit yourself.
You've been waiting a lifetime
to see dinosaurs.
Just thought you'd be interested in seeing
one they stopped showing to the public.
But... whatevs.
It's only a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
Ka-ching!
Where's this tunnel go?
This tu-hu-nel is part
of an underground network
connecting the whole island.
This is how the big dogs get around.
You're actually looking
at a Jurassic World VIP, kid.
[hatch hisses]
Kenji?
-[lights click]
-[electricity crackles]
You still bummed about that genetics lab?
-[Brooklynn] Okay, Dr. Wu, you're on.
-[clears throat]
Hello, I'm Dr. Henry Wu, PhD.
Welcome to one of our satellite
Jurassic World genetics labs.
I like to say that creating
a dinosaur takes TIME--
T, technology; I, ingenuity; and M-E, me.
Whoa! Eyeball! Ooh!
-[shudders]
-[camera shutter clicks]
Dr. Wu, what's that?
Tree frog DNA.
Unfortunately, I--
-[gasps] What's that?
-Siberian mammoth remains extracted for--
Ooh! What's down that hall?
My private office.
It's restricted.
You guys, look!
Oh, I think one of these eggs
is about to hatch.
That's not possible.
That ankylosaurus
has only been incubating for ten weeks.
[Yasmina gasps] Is that a tail?
-Oh-hh. Oh, ew, ew, ew!
-[squelches]
-Get it off me! Get it--
-[camera shutter clicks]
[grunts]
[squealing]
-[chuckles] Aw!
-Sweet!
One of its head bumps
is bigger than the other!
Asymmetry? In my lab?
Aw! Wow.
She's so... tiny.
But she won't stay tiny for long, right?
That's the idea.
All the dinosaurs go through
an accelerated growth cycle.
They're supposed to incubate for 13 weeks
with no noticeable defects,
but apparently this one slipped through.
[Darius] For real, though,
where are you taking me?
Are we seeing a secret T. rex
or a rare sauropod?
Kid, Kenji has something better
than a rare sauropod.
We're headed to where they quarantine
the dinos that are too aggro.
The last one I saw here
was some kind of carna...
carna-something.
Hold up. Carnotaur?
[muffled] We're gonna see a carnotaurus?
[normal voice] That's, like,
one of my top five favorite dinos!
Sweet, right?
The park board actually offered
to name it after me,
but I was like, "Nah, I'll hold out
for something cooler."
But I figured you'd like it,
you know, as a thanks,
which is what this is for, uh, you know,
not being a narc when--
So, there's, like, a carnotaurus
right-- right up there?
Obviously.
Like my boy Masrani always says,
"When Kenji promises, Kenji delivers."
-[buzzer blares]
-Phew!
Let's go melt your nerd-brain, junior.
[Darius grunts]
Uh, you do know where you're going, right?
Trust me, I got this on lock.
The pen, heh, is...
that way.
What am I doing?
[hatch whirs]
-Oof!
-Huh?
Oh! Hey!
Sammy! Uh, what are you doing out here?
I was just... [chuckles]
This place ought to come with a GPS.
I really gotta go.
I... I think there's a bathroom
on the other end of the hall, actually.
-So...
-Thanks! See you back there!
[footsteps thudding]
[man] Doctor!
We have those results
you were looking for.
Very well.
Okay, Brooklanders,
let's see if top-secret Jurassic World
intel is cool enough for you.
[camera shutter clicks]
-[whirring]
-[gasps]
"E750.
Clinical trial results"?
"Classified"!
Jackpot!
-[mouse clicks]
-[beeps]
-[gasps]
-[alarm blares]
Uh...
-Hmm...
-[keyboard clacks]
[scoffs] Dang it!
"Indominus rex"?
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
I thought the door said "restroom"?
-[dinosaur bellows]
-[Kenji grunting]
[Darius and Kenji grunting, panting]
-[buzzing]
-[grunting]
Where is that stupid fence?
Kenji, maybe we should head back.
We don't wanna get caught
and cause trouble with your dad.
What does my dad have to do with anything?
Dude's barely around.
He's not worrying about me.
What?
Then what was all the,
[imitates Kenji] "My whole life I've been
trying to make my dad proud, junior."
Oh, right.
I was lying...
'cause of the whole not wanting
to get in trouble and sent home thing.
Forgive me for not wanting to spend
another summer alone.
In fact, when you really think about it,
this is on you for being so gullible.
[normal voice] I can't believe this.
There is no carnotaurus, is there?
Hey, I keep it honest!
Except this morning.
And, like, a bunch of other times today.
-But I'm telling the truth about this!
-Great!
I'm out here for no reason,
I'll probably get sent home,
and it's all because I believed you!
Fine, whatever.
Last time I try to do something nice
for a dumb kid.
[metal clangs]
[Kenji] Kenji delivers.
You know this park
like the back of your hand, right?
Uh, duh!
So, you definitely know which side
of the fence the carnotaurus is on?
[wings flapping]
-[growling]
-[both gasp]
[snarling]
[Kenji] Uh... [whimpers]
-[Ben cooing]
-[trilling]
Well, that's it, Ben.
Looks like you live here now.
-Time for you all to leave.
-[Brooklynn] Hey!
Clearly, this group
has no respect for my lab.
-But what about Bumpy?
-Aw, Bumpy!
You gave it a name. That's precious!
The asset will soon be released
into a herd of ankylosauruses.
Then she'll be their problem,
just like you all will cease to be
my problem when you leave.
All right, bup-bup-bup-bup-bup!
Hit the road. We are not wanted here.
[Bumpy cooing]
[squealing]
-[roaring]
-[both panting]
[both grunt]
Don't leave me, man!
-[Darius whimpers]
-[roars]
[Darius panting, whimpering]
Dude! It's gaining!
It's fast, but not on turns!
Zig-zag, on my count!
-One, two, three!
-[roars]
[roars]
[both panting]
Up ahead!
[grunts]
[screams, pants]
[both grunting]
[snarling]
-[roars]
-[whimpers] Kenji!
Are you kidding me, Kenji?
Come on!
-Come on!
-[roars]
[both grunt]
[roaring]
[laughs, grunts]
Diddums da the big dino
hurt his widdle nose?
You think you're slick, Toro?
You got nothin'!
Toro. 'Cause-- 'Cause of the horns.
Yeah, I get it.
Hey, Toro, your arms are...
pretty much vestigial at this point! Ha!
Yeah, boy! That's what's up!
That's what--
-[clangs]
-[both yelp]
Uh...
What time are they supposed to get
back from the lab?
[both panting]
Hey, guys.
Why are you two so out of breath?
Just doing the job we're told.
How was the field trip?
Oh, well, um, you know,
Ben fell in love with a dinosaur,
and Super Star here
got us booted from the lab.
-That is not what happen--
-How'd poop patrol go?
-Uh...
-Awesome!
-You all should've seen how I owned--
-This valuable experience!
Um, learned a lot about ourselves
and, uh... yep!
[sniffs] Oh! Well, then, hit the showers.
And maybe stay in there for a while?
Use soap.
Lots of soap!
Two near-death experiences in two days?
We can't tell anyone about Toro
or we're definitely getting sent home.
[sighs]
I can't believe no one will know
I saved your life.
I'll know, Kenji.
[sighs] Thanks. [chuckles]
So, we even now, Darius?
Yeah, we're even.
You do know farts
didn't kill the dinosaurs, right?
Prove me wrong, yo.
There is a lot of proof--
Okay, first I'm going to take
a five-hour shower,
and then tonight we're going over
how the atmosphere works.
[crickets chirping]
[rustling]
[whirring]
[trilling]
[powers up]
[theme music playing]